All pirates searching for the treasure One Piece must brave the second half of the Grand Line.
These wild and dangerous seas are known as the New World.
Gold Roger and his crew were the only men to ever chart these waters and learn all the secrets they held.
For the rest of the pirates of the world, this has proven to be the end of the road, a graveyard of dreams.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body became rubber after eating the gum gum fruit, set sail into the New World with his faithful crew.
I'm going to be the king of the pirates!
During their journey to the New World, Luffy and his crew arrive on Fishman Island, which is located 10,000 meters below sea level.
The Fishman Pirates, led by Hordy Jones and assisted by Vander Decken, plot to overthrow King Neptune.
It's not long before the Straw Hats get pulled into the conflict.
Thankfully, two individuals rose up on Fishman Island, individuals who had helped change the course of our beleaguered history.
The first was Queen Otohime.
Then there was him, the legendary hero named Fisher Tiger, who freed countless slaves.
Nevertheless, they fought for our future, and both of their tales end in tragedy.
A hero who freed the slaves, an adventurer tiger!
I'm going to tell you an important story from our past.
Regretfully, the incidents within this tale set in motion Arlong's rampage in the East Blue.
I hope this can bring us to some understanding.
Yeah, I'm listening.
I'm listening.
Before I get into the details, you must know how our world was 16 years ago.
Move it!
Please!
Stop him!
He's getting away with our money!
Somebody do something!
Just stay out of my way, got it?
Because you don't want to see what I'll do to this girl if you try to be a hero.
Huh?
Your Majesty?
Wait, don't go that way!
You shouldn't involve yourself with such a thing!
This is not our responsibility!
Please, wait!
Queen Otohime!
Who's that?
Don't come any closer!
I'll shoot!
I warned you!
I missed?
Dammit!
Get back!
I missed!
Damn it!
Get back!
I missed!
Damn it!
Get back!
I missed!
I missed you!
I got you!
Wait, isn't that Queen Otohime?
My hair!
Hurry, Doctor!
Your Highness, let me take a look.
It's fractured, I'm afraid.
She hit him once and broke her hand?
It's fine.
Queen Otohime!
The Queen?
Why would you do something as foolish and selfish as robbing your fellow people?
What do you care? Like a rich member of the royal family could understand.
I got ten kids waiting at home, and all they do is cry, cause they're hungry!
All the more reason!
No! Queen Otohime!
You must stop hitting him, please!
They're much too delicate, you will only make your injury worse!
I don't care! I have to do this!
Even if my hand must shatter to pieces, he will learn his lesson!
Do you think your children would be happy if they knew the truth?
If they knew their father was a thief?
You should be trying to live your life in a way that makes them proud!
However,
I owe you
an apology.
Please forgive me!
Even though I'm your queen,
I've been completely ignorant to the hardships that one of my subjects has been forced to endure.
My heart can't take it.
Your worries and your pain,
they're killing me!
You must have had a reason for doing this!
I don't know.
It's not that I wanted to.
But I,
I felt like there was no other way.
Somebody sent fire to my store
and stole all my money.
We couldn't save anything
before we burned down.
Just like that,
I didn't have a job.
My debt started piling up,
and now my kids are starving.
I'm sorry that happened.
And I understand.
I really do,
but...
It's wrong!
If you do to others what was done to you,
the cycle will never end!
I'm sorry!
No, I'm sorry!
We weren't there for you in your time of need,
so that makes us accountable as well.
Your Highness,
it's really not your fault.
But that's a terribly generous thing for you to say.
It's still wrong, though!
I know!
Then don't do it!
You've changed me!
And my whole life!
Thank you so much!
After seeing how much you cried for me,
I'll never steal again!
I know that you won't!
Best of luck in the future!
We're so lucky to have a member of the royal family
who's not afraid to share the troubles
of common people like us.
She nearly had me crying along with her,
though I certainly hope she doesn't break her hand next time.
Our Queen Otohime is a one-of-a-kind ruler,
or I can tell you that much!
She has such a kind heart.
And look there!
Even the children of the kingdom adore her!
Queen Otohime!
I'll do everything I can to protect your smiling faces!
You're nose is running terribly!
If I don't reprimand you for it, who will?
You look ridiculous with mucus dribbling out of just one side.
It's more dignified to dribble from both nostrils.
Such a tender moment!
I guess so.
No one was more passionate or loving.
Every day Queen Otohime descended from the palace to address the nation.
That day was no different.
The time has come for us to relocate the Ryugu kingdom to the surface.
Our skins are different colors,
and we do not look the same.
These are the things the humans say in order to avoid understanding us
and our unique way of life.
But that's why we should move.
To understand each other.
Our worlds are 10,000 meters apart.
So, that is also the distance between our ways of thinking.
I know you're afraid.
After all, the humans who come to our island are pirates and criminals.
And the humans who buy our people from kidnappers like them
are cruel and corrupt nobles.
It's true that our only exposure to humans has been negative,
but that doesn't mean we can judge all humans the same.
I believe in my heart that there are good ones among them as well.
And thus, to improve relations,
we must move our kingdom to be under the same sun.
It is my goal to express our intention
to relocate above sea level at this year's world summit.
But in order to do that, I need all of you to sign.
While, uh, I admit it sounds like a good idea in theory, but...
Just the thought of living near humans is...
Well...
I understand how you feel.
However, this is our chance to make a real change
rather than suffering in silence.
Please!
Look, I'm sorry, but...
No.
It's no use.
History can't be fought so easily.
Hello, everyone!
I'm home!
Ah!
Shirahoshi!
I hope you can forgive me, darling.
Mommy didn't mean to be so late.
Even with your nose running on one side,
you're still beautiful.
We stayed with her the entire time you were gone
so she'd feel safe, Mother.
It's true, Mother!
We did!
I have such brave sons.
But what happened to your hand?
Are you okay?
Oh, don't worry, dear.
It's nothing.
See?
To ensure you all have a bright future,
I would suffer.
So much worse than this.
If Queen Otohime wants to make announcements,
she really should do them by video
rather than going down there in person.
Unfortunately, thanks to her strong observation, Haki,
doing something like that would go against her very nature.
She would rather win the hearts of the citizens in person
than from the palace.
It's one of Otohime's guiding principles.
Not even I can change that.
She's constantly putting her life at risk
with all those human pirates coming and going on the island.
We know you're on good terms with Whitebeard,
and to some extent his influence can protect her while she's there.
But anything could happen.
That is a fact of which she is all too aware.
And yet, it does nothing to deter her.
For the world Otohime dreams of
is far more than a simple fantasy.
After all, unifying our peoples was also the ambition of our ancestors,
although they were never able to make that vision a reality.
What?
I'm afraid that I don't follow your majesty.
I can't stop Otohime from doing what she thinks is right.
So it's up to you to keep her safe.
Yes, sir.
Hey, where you going, fish girl?
Sir?
How about some special service?
I'm sorry.
I don't think I know what you mean.
Huh?
Come on now, don't be such a snob.
We know how you fish men are.
What's wrong?
You punks got something to say?
Get out of here.
You're ruining my meal.
Sorry.
This Queen Otohime certainly seemed unique, if nothing else.
Sounds like she was a crybaby, too.
Did you inherit that from her?
Um, yes.
I suppose I did.
Hold on.
You used to be a soldier for the kingdom?
When you grow up in the fish man district,
where you know nothing but fighting,
there aren't a lot of career path options available to you.
You don't say.
That's rough.
Is that where you're from, Hachi?
It sounds like a pretty bad neighborhood.
It was.
Believe me.
Originally, it was an orphanage for children with no living relatives.
But in time, the orphanage became too much for the administrators to handle.
Before long, it became a lawless area that caught the eye of delinquents from all over the island.
Back then, Fisher Tiger was the closest thing we had to a leader,
but he left to have his own adventures.
I'd been his second in command, but I went on to join Neptune's army.
And despite being fish men,
Macro and some others started helping the kidnappers.
As for everyone else,
they all left, following their own pursuits.
Until one day...
Please, give them back!
Oh, you almost had them that time.
Hey, knock it off!
Do you realize how hard it was for her to get all those signatures?
Yeah, and you realize I don't care, right?
These papers aren't gonna change a damn thing!
Get it?
Hey, cut it out!
You fish men district reject!
Huh?
You think you're better than me because of where I'm from?
Let go of me!
You got it backwards, pal.
I'm the captain of the Arlong Pirates,
and you're just a nobody.
I clean up all the human garbage you let run wild.
Pirates so pathetic, they can't even breathe in the water.
You guys in Neptune's army should be thanking us.
Maybe I should beat a donation out of you.
Please, I'm in trouble over here.
He's gonna kill me, Boss Jinbei.
Jinbei.
All right, punk.
Just put the rookie down and walk away.
He's weak, but he's one of my men.
And as for those papers you've taken,
they may not mean anything to us,
but they're quite important to her majesty.
Give them back.
That's Boss Jinbei of Neptune's army!
It'll help us!
Yeah!
They call you Boss!
How'd you get that kind of respect?
Sounds more like the title of a gang leader than a soldier, though.
I told you to let him go, Arlong.
All right, fine.
Here.
So are we all good now, brother?
Huh?
Brother?
It's been a while.
But I can always tell when someone's from the Fistman district.
Don't lump me in with you.
You went off and became a lousy pirate.
You're scum.
Hmph.
Don't call me that, brother.
Then how about trash?
Oh, that's it!
Doesn't matter where we're from.
You can't talk to me like that!
Hey!
Hey, everyone!
Fisher Tiger's come home!
I don't believe it!
Tiger's back!
He's here!
How is the trip?
It's brother time!
Finally made it back!
Hi, Jinbei.
And Arlong.
It sure looks like you two have been doing well.
That was quite a lengthy voyage you took.
Yeah, an eventful one, too.
Now that you're here, you can see my ship!
Later.
First, I need to go to the Ryugu Palace.
I can show you the way.
He has no need for a lousy pirate.
Huh?
That's not how Big Brother feels about me at all!
Heh heh heh.
Come on, guys.
Don't fight.
You're telling me you're going to free the slaves?
Surely you can't be serious.
I'm afraid I am.
I can't stand it anymore.
The thought of our people living a nightmare.
Even as we're speaking right now, our people are being treated like animals.
Yes, but...
My mind's made up.
I just wanted to tell you before I did anything, since it's going to cause you a lot of trouble.
Despite that, I ask that you keep this to yourselves.
Tell me, why are you so adamant about this?
What did you see on your trip?
I saw human nature.
Not long after that, Tiger made his move.
This is bad!
What's the problem?
Oh, good, I found you, boss.
It's about Tiger.
It seems he attacked the Celestial Dragons.
No, that can't be true.
Fisher Tiger unleashed all-out war on the Holy Land of Mariejoie.
For freeing the slaves, he forever became a hero to our people
and a criminal to the world government.
Consider this my resignation from the army.
Jinbei!
You would walk away from your sworn duty?
Much to my surprise, I've enjoyed my role as this island's protector.
However, my obligation to this kingdom does not outweigh my debt of honor.
It looks like Big Brother Tai has finally made his move.
All right, O-Long Pirates.
From here on, we work for Fisher Tiger.
Let's go, men!
Before long, every ruffian from the Fishman District had assembled to fight by his side.
How does it feel to be lumped in with lousy pirate scum?
Come.
It's us against the world from now on.
If you're truly ready for the days ahead, then step up!
All who accepted the sun mark that day became brothers.
It was a symbol that enveloped the brand given to slaves.
No longer could anyone distinguish which of us had always been free
and which of us had to fight to reclaim that freedom.
And that's how a bunch of lowlifes from the Fishman District rose up as the Sun Pirates.
Fisher Tiger attacks the Holy Land of Marie Joie, freeing those enslaved by the Celestial Dragons.
As his journey continues, he encounters a human girl with a tragic past who he vows to reunite with her family.
Unfortunately, his actions have drawn the attention of a very deadly adversary.
On the next One Piece, Kizaru appears! A trap to catch Tiger!
I'm gonna be king of the pirates!